http://www.sunmarkbank.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content.
WHAT DOES SUNMARK COMMUNITY BANK DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Account transactions and checking account information
Credit history and credit scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customer’s personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customer’s personal information; the reasons SunMark Community Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does SunMark Community Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don’t share
Questions?
Call 478-783-4036 or go to www.sunmarkbank.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
SunMark Community Bank
What we do
How does SunMark Community Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does SunMark Community Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
pay your bills or apply for a loan
Use your credit card or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, and other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
SunMark Bancshares Inc.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
SunMark Community Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
SunMark Community Bank does not jointly market.
